Finding aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) records, 1900-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical files
  - 1992
    - Academic and Multicultural Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 135)
    - Admissions, Office of Undergraduate (Box 135)
    - Aerospace Engineering, Office of (Box 135)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 135)
    - Afro-American and African Studies, Center for (Box 135)
    - Anthropology, Department of (LSA) (Box 135)
    - Alumni Association (Box 135)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 135)
    - Art, School of (Box 135)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures, Department (Box 135)
    - Asian Studies (Box 135)
    - Astronomy, Department of (LSA) (Box 135)
    - Atmospheric, Oceanic and Space Sciences, Department of (ENG) (Box 135)
    - Biological Station (Box 135)
    - Biology, Department of (LSA) (Box 135)
    - Biological Gardens (Box 135)
    - Buildings (Box 135)
    - Budget (Box 135)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 135)
    - Campaign for Michigan (Box 135)
    - Career Planning and Placement, Office of (Box 135)
    - Carmel (Box 135)
    - Chemistry, Department of (LSA) (Box 135)
    - Chemical Engineering, Department of (ENG) (Box 135)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 135)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 135)
    - Clements, Library (Box 135)
    - Commencement (Box 135)
    - Commission for Women (Box 135)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 135)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program/Opportunity Program (Box 135)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 135)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 135)
    - Development, Vice President for (Box 135)
    - Economic Development, State and Ann Arbor (Box 135)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 135)
    - Economics, Department of (LSA) (Box 135)
    - Education, Department of (Box 135)
    - Education of Women, Center for (Box 135)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Department of (Box 135)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 135)
    - English Composition Board (Box 135)
    - English, Department of (LSA) (Box 135)
    - Enrollment (Box 135)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute for (Box 135)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office of (Box 135)
    - Extension Services (Box 135)
    - Faculty (Box 135)
    - Fees (Box 135)
    - Film and Video Studies, Program in (Box 135)
    - Financial Aid, Office of Student (Box 136)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief (Box 136)
    - Flint Campus (Box 136)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 136)
    - General Counsel (Box 136)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (LSA) (Box 136)
    - Germanic Languages and Literatures, Department of (LSA) (Box 136)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 136)
    - Government Relations, Vice President for (Box 136)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 136)
    - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (Box 136)
    - History, Department of (LSA) (Box 136)
    - History of Art, Department of (LSA) (Box 136)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 136)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 136)
    - Honors
      - Faculty (Box 136)
      - Student (Box 136)
    - Honors Council (LSA) (Box 136)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 136)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 136)
    - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 136)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering, Department of (ENG) (Box 136)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 136)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 136)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (Box 136)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - International Center (Box 136)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 136)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 136)
    - Kelsey Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 136)
    - Kinesiology, Division of (Box 136)
    - Kresge Hearing Research Institute Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute for (Box 136)
    - Law School (Box 136)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 136)
    - Libraries (Box 136)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 136)
    - Mathematics, Department of (LSA) (Box 136)
    - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics, Department of (ENG) (Box 136)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 136)
    - Medical Center, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 136)
    - Michigan Historical Collection (includes Bentley Library) (Box 136)
    - Michigan League (Box 136)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 136)
    - Michigan Radio (Box 136)
    - Michigan Union (Box 136)
    - Middle Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 136)
    - Museum of Art (Box 136)
    - Natural Resources and Environment, School of (Box 136)
    - Natural Science Museum (Box 136)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Department of (Box 136)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (LSA) (Box 136)
    - Nursing School of (Box 136)
    - News and Information Services (Box 136)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 136)
    - Personnel (Box 137)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 137)
    - Philosophy, Department of (LSA) (Box 137)
    - Phoenix Project, Michigan Memorial (Box 137)
    - Physics, Department of (LSA) (Box 137)
    - Plant Extension, Plant Operations (Box 137)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 137)
    - Population Planning, Center for (Public Health) (Box 137)
    - Population Studies Center (LSA) (Box 137)
    - President, Office of the (Box 137)
    - Psychology, Department of (LSA) (Box 137)
    - Public Health School of (Box 137)
    - Public Policy, School of (Box 137)
    - Public Safety and Security, Department of, 3 folders (Box 137)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 137)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 137)
    - Regents, 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Religion, Studies in (Box 137)
    - Research, Office of the Vice President for (Box 137)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 137)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 137)
    - Residential College (Box 137)
    - Romance Languages and Literature, Department of (LSA) (Box 137)
    - ROTC (Box 137)
    - Russel, Henry, Lectures and Awards (Box 137)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 137)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 137)
    - Slavic Languages and Literature, Department of (LSA) (Box 137)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 137)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 137)
    - Sociology, Department of (LSA) (Box 137)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President (Box 137)
    - Student Activities (Box 137)
    - Student Publications, Board for (Box 137)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 138)
    - University Health Service (Box 138)
    - University Housing (Box 138)
    - University Musical Society (Box 138)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 138)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 138)
    - University Relations, Vice President for (Box 138)
    - Women (General) (Box 138)
    - Women Studies Program (Box 138)
  - 1993
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice-President and Provost (Box 138)
    - Admissions Office (Box 138)
    - Aerospace Engineering, Department of (Box 138)
    - Afroamerican and African Studies (Box 138)
    - Alumni Association (Box 138)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 138)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 138)
    - Art, School of (Box 138)
    - Arts, Vice Provost for (Box 138)
    - Asian Studies (Box 138)
    - Astronomy, Department of (LSA) (Box 138)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 138)
    - Biological Station (Box 138)
    - Biology, Dept. of (Box 138)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 138)
    - Budget (Box 138)
    - Buildings (Box 138)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 138)
    - Cancer Research Institute (Box 138)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 138)
    - Carmel (Box 138)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 138)
    - Chemistry (Box 138)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 138)
    - Classical Studies (Box 138)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 138)
    - Commencement (Box 138)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 138)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program (Box 138)
    - Consumer Attitudes, Survey of (Box 138)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 138)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 138)
    - Development and Communication Office (Box 138)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (CRED) (Box 138)
    - Economic development-State and Ann Arbor (Box 138)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 138)
    - Education, School of (Box 138)
    - Education of Women, Center for the (Box 138)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) (Box 138)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 138)
    - English, Department of (LSA) (Box 138)
    - Enrollment (Box 138)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 138)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office for (Box 138)
    - Extension Service (Box 138)
    - Faculty (Box 138)
    - Fees (Box 138)
    - Film and Video Studies, Program (Box 138)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 138)
    - Financial (Box 138)
    - Flint Campus (Box 138)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 138)
    - General Counsel (Box 138)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (Box 138)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 138)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 138)
    - Government Relations, VP for (Box 138)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 138)
    - History, Department of (LSA) (Box 138)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 138)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 138)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 138)
    - Honors (Box 139)
      - Faculty (Box 139)
      - Student (Box 139)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 139)
    - Human Resources and Affirmative Action (Box 139)
    - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 139)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 139)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 139)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 139)
    - International Center (Box 139)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (Box 139)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 139)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 139)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 139)
    - Kinesiology (Box 139)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 139)
    - Law School (Box 139)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 139)
    - Libraries (Box 139)
    - Linguistics (Box 139)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 139)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 139)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice-Provost for (Box 139)
    - Medical Center (Box 139)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (includes Bentley Library) (Box 139)
    - Michigan Law Review (Box 139)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 139)
    - Michigan Radio (Box 139)
    - Michigan Sea Grant College Program (Box 139)
    - Michigan Union (Box 139)
    - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 139)
    - Minority Affairs, Vice-Provost for (Box 139)
    - Music, School of (Box 139)
    - Natural Resources and Environment, School of (Box 139)
    - Natural Science Museums (Box 139)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 139)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 139)
    - News and Information Services (Box 139)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 139)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 139)
    - Personnel (Box 139)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 139)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 139)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 139)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 139)
    - Plant Extension; Plant Operations (Box 139)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 139)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 139)
    - Population Planning, Center for (Public Health) (Box 139)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 139)
    - President, Office of (Box 139)
    - Psychology Department of (LSA) (Box 139)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 139)
    - Public Policy School of (Box 139)
    - Public Safety and Security, Dept. of (Box 139)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 139)
    - Regents (Box 139)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 139)
    - Religion, Dept. of (Box 139)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 139)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President for (Box 139)
    - Romance Languages and Literatures (Box 140)
    - ROTC (Box 140)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 140)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 140)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 140)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 140)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 140)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 140)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 140)
    - Solar Car, Maize and Blue (Box 140)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 140)
    - Student Activities (Box 140)
    - Student Affairs, Office of the Vice President for (Box 140)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 140)
    - Student Publications (Box 140)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 140)
    - University Health Service (Box 140)
    - University Housing (Box 140)
    - University Musical Society (Box 140)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 140)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 140)
    - University Relations, VP for (Box 140)
    - Women (General) (Box 140)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 140)
  - 1994
    - Academic Affairs, Provost and Vice-President for (Box 140)
    - Academic and Multicultural Affairs, Vice-President for (Box 140)
    - Admissions, Office of Undergraduate (Box 140)
    - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (Box 140)
    - Alumni Association (Box 140)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 140)
    - Art, School of (Box 140)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures, Department of (LSA) (Box 140)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 140)
    - Atmospheric, Oceanic and Space Sciences, Department of (Engin.) (Box 140)
    - Biological Station (Box 140)
    - Biology, Department of (LSA) (Box 140)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 140)
    - Budget (Box 140)
    - Buildings (Box 140)
    - Business Administration (Box 140)
    - Campaign for Michigan (Box 140)
    - Career Planning and Placement, Office of (Box 140)
    - Chemistry, Department of (LSA) (Box 140)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 140)
    - Clements Library (Box 140)
    - Commencement (Box 140)
    - Communication, Department of (LSA) (Box 140)
    - Consumer Attitudes, Survey of (Box 140)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 140)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 140)
    - Development, Vice-President for (Box 140)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research (CRED) (Box 141)
    - Economic Development-State and Ann Arbor (Box 141)
    - Economics, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - Education, School of (Box 141)
    - Education of Women, Center for the (CEW) (Box 141)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Department of (Eng.) (Box 141)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 141)
    - English, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - English Composition Board (Box 141)
    - Enrollment (Box 141)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 141)
    - Extension Service (Box 141)
    - Faculty (Box 141)
    - Fees (Box 141)
    - Film and Video Studies, Program in (Box 141)
    - Financial Aid, Office of Student (Box 141)
    - Flint Campus (Box 141)
    - General Counsel (Box 141)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 141)
    - Government Relations, Vice-President for (Box 141)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham (Box 141)
    - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (Box 141)
    - History, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 141)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 141)
    - Honors (Faculty) (Box 141)
    - Honors (Student) (Box 141)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 141)
    - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 141)
    - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 141)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 141)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 141)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 141)
    - International Center (Box 141)
    - International Institute (Box 141)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (ICPSR) (Box 141)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 141)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 141)
    - Kelsey Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 141)
    - Kinesiology, Division of (Box 141)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (ILIR) (Box 141)
    - Law School (Box 141)
    - Libraries (Box 141)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts (LSA), College of (Box 141)
    - Mathematics, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice-Provost for (Box 141)
    - Medical Center (Box 141)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (includes Bentley Library) (Box 141)
    - Michigan Mandate (Box 141)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 141)
    - Michigan Radio (Box 141)
    - Michigan Sea Grant College Program (Engin.) (Box 141)
    - Michigan Union (Box 141)
    - Music, School of (Box 141)
    - Museum of Art (Box 141)
    - Natural Resources and Environment, School of (Box 141)
    - Natural Science Museums (Box 141)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Department of (Eng.) (Box 141)
    - News and Information Services (Box 141)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 141)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 141)
    - Personnel (Box 141)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 141)
    - Philosophy, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - Phoenix Project, Michigan Memorial (Box 141)
    - Plant Extension, Plant Operations (Box 141)
    - Political Science, Department of (LSA) (Box 141)
    - Population Studies Center (LSA) (Box 141)
    - President, Office of the (Box 141)
    - Psychology, Department of (LSA) (Box 142)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 142)
    - Public Policy, School of (Box 142)
    - Public Safety and Security, Department of (Box 142)
    - Regents (Box 142)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 142)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President for (Box 142)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (DRDA) (Box 142)
    - ROTC (Box 142)
    - Russell Lectures and Awards, Henry (Box 142)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 142)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (IST) (Box 142)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 142)
    - Social Research, Institute for (ISR) (Box 142)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 142)
    - Sociology, Department of (LSA) (Box 142)
    - Student Affairs, Vice-President for (Box 142)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 142)
    - Student Publications, Board for (Box 142)
    - Transportation Research Institute, U-M (UMTRI) (Box 142)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 142)
    - University Health Service (Box 142)
    - University Housing (Box 142)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 142)
    - University Musical Society (Box 142)
    - University Relations, Vice-President for (Box 142)
    - Women (General) (Box 142)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 142)
  - 1995
    - Academic Affairs, Provost and Vice President for (Box 142)
    - Academic and Multicultural Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 142)
    - Academic Rankings (includes U.S. News and World Report rankings) (Box 142)
    - Admissions, Office of Undergraduate (Box 142)
    - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (Box 142)
    - Alumni Association (Box 142)
    - Anthropology, Department of (LSA) (Box 142)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 142)
    - Art, School of (Box 142)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures, Department of (Box 142)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 142)
    - Atmospheric, Oceanic, and Space Sciences, Department of (Box 142)
    - Biological Station (Box 142)
    - Biology, Department of (Box 142)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 142)
    - Budget (Box 142)
    - Buildings (Box 142)
    - Business Administration (Box 142)
    - Career Planning and Placement, Office of (Box 143)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 143)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 143)
    - Clements Library (Box 143)
    - Commencement (Box 143)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 143)
    - Community Service Learning (Box 143)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 143)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 143)
    - Development, Vice President for (Box 143)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 143)
    - Economic Development, State and Ann Arbor (Box 143)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 143)
    - Education, School of (Box 143)
    - Education of Women, Center for the (Box 143)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Department of (Box 143)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 143)
    - English, Department of (Box 143)
    - English Language Institute (Box 143)
    - Enrollment (Box 143)
    - Extension Service (Box 143)
    - Faculty (Box 143)
    - Fees (Box 143)
    - Film and Video Studies, Program in (Box 143)
    - Financial Aid, Office of Student (Box 143)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief (Box 143)
    - Flint Campus (Box 143)
    - General Counsel (Box 143)
    - Geological Sciences, Department of (Box 143)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 143)
    - Government Relations, Vice President for (Box 143)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 143)
    - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, Center for (Box 143)
    - History, Department of (Box 143)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 143)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 143)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 143)
    - Honors (Faculty) (Box 143)
    - Honors (Student) (Box 143)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 143)
    - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 143)
    - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 143)
    - Information Technology, Vice-Provost for (Box 143)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 143)
    - International Center (Box 143)
    - International Institute (Box 143)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research (ISR) (Box 143)
    - Judaic Studies Program (Box 143)
    - Kelsey Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 143)
    - Kinesiology, Division of (Box 143)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (ILIR) (Box 143)
    - Law School (Box 143)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 143)
    - Libraries (Box 143)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 143)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 143)
    - Medical Center (Box 143)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (includes Bentley Library) (Box 143)
    - Michigan League (Box 143)
    - Michigan Mandate (Box 143)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 143)
    - Michigan Radio (Box 143)
    - Michigan Union (Box 143)
    - Museum of Art (Box 143)
    - Music, School of (Box 143)
    - Natural Resources and Environment, School of (Box 143)
    - Natural Science Museums (Box 143)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Department of (Box 143)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 143)
    - News and Information Services (Box 143)
    - Nuclear Engineering and Radiological Science, Department of (Box 143)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 143)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health (Box 143)
    - Personnel (Box 143)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 143)
    - Phoenix Project, Michigan Memorial (Box 144)
    - Photo Packets (Box 144)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 144)
    - Plant Extension, Plant Operations (Box 144)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 144)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 144)
    - President, Office of (Box 144)
    - Presidential Search (Box 144)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 144)
    - Public Health, School of (includes 40th anniversary of Polio vaccine announcement) (Box 144)